Well, the time has come.
For those of you who don't know,
every year my mother has a Christmas tree theme.
Y'all, it's a Smart, Funny, and Black tree!
We've had flamingos as a theme.
Notice the attention to detail.
I'm sitting here eating my dinner,
and from her room my mom says,
you saw your tree?
We've had small doses.
This is hilarious!
Yes, you went in!
Sharla, you made the tree twice!
Oh, Fishmas tree, oh, Fishmas tree.
Well, the theme is art.
Why are you talking like a customer service agent
at Caribbean Air?
And then we have Santa Claus,
but then look what Santa Claus has in his backpack.
What is that?
Toilet paper, black cleanser, you know.
So let's keep the tradition going.
Join us and the SEAL squad
as we reveal my mom's Christmas tree theme
for 2022.
Only happening at theamandiverse.com
where all the cool kids hang.
Well, at least the ones that just really like my stuff.
See you there with some Christmas cheer.